liquidhearth.com 2018-01-28

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. We provide this policy to better protect you, and to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

This privacy policy applies to all Team Liquid website properties, including teamliquid.net, liquidhearth.com, liquiddota.com, liquidlegends.net, teamliquidpro.com and any standalone partner websites that are made by us.

## The Information We Collect

During user registration, we collect the following information:

Username  
Email address (if provided)  
IP address  
Birthday (if provided)  
Country (if provided)

The username you supply will be used as an identifier when posting content to our website. An email address is required to register if signing up on our website as your login details will be sent to it. Your email address will not be publicly displayed on any part of the website, but it will be visible to Team Liquid staff. Your IP address is recorded to monitor abuse resulting from multiple registrations under the same IP address, spam bots, link farmers, etc.

If you choose to register using a 3rd party service, such as a social network, that 3rd party will provide us with a unique identifier so that we may identify you on future logins. We do not store your social media username or any other details that may incidentally be provided to us when using social media logins. Your social media username will be used only during the first login in order to provide a recommended Team Liquid username.

As part of our site features, we offer a forum and other features on which you can freely post any text. If you choose to disclose personally identifying information, be aware that Team Liquid is a public web site and anyone is able to read your posts, so there is no expectation of privacy for user-generated content. Where applicable, we will moderate any posts that violate US law in regards to information disclosed about other individuals.

The website features a private messaging system which allows you to send message to other users on the website. The messages you exchange over the private messaging system can only be read by the recipient user account or Team Liquid administrators. The Team Liquid administrators will only access private message details if they suspect the message might be spam / advertising or otherwise malicious in nature, or if required to do so by law. We cannot be responsible for any disclosure of private message contents by the recipient.

As an optional feature of the user profile page, you may upload an image such as a photo of yourself. This image will be visible to other users through your Team Liquid profile page. At any time, you can modify or delete this image through your user profile settings.

During your usage of the website, your browser will open connections and send requests to our web server. The server will log each request with your IP address, date and time, status code, browser version (user agent), HTTP referrer and the resource requested.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/).

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide to better identify yourself to other users. Your username and country can be viewed by anyone visiting our website. Your username will identify you in any posts you make to the website forums.

Your email address will never be shared with third parties for marketing, spam, or promotional activities. We may use your email address to identify you in moderation actions, for instance when a user creates multiple accounts and uses them maliciously. Your email address will also be used to reset your password, though if you lose access to that particular email, we can change it or reset your password manually. From time to time, we may use your email address to send low-volume important site announcements. If you do not wish to receive these announcements, an opt-out link will be provided in each email and you may disable the emails at any time through your profile settings.

The web server logs are used to troubleshoot issues with the website and to generate aggregate site statistics. Should we determine that a problem with the site is being caused by a particular IP address, we may match the IP address in the log files with registered user accounts in order to initiate contact with the user causing problems.

Except as where required by law, we will never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Use Of Cookies

We use a first party session cookie ("SID") to track your session across the site. This cookie is temporary and is necessary for basic functionality of the website such as maintaining your logged in status and providing security against cross site request forgery. The cookie will be deleted automatically when you close your browser. If you choose to log in to our site, we will set a first party cookie ("tlnet") that remembers your username and password, so on subsequent visits to our site you will remain logged in.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer to help the website analyse how visitors use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. 

This website uses Google AdSense. AdSense uses cookies to help serve the ads it displays on our websites that display AdSense ads or are participating in Google certified ad networks. When you visit our websites, a cookie may be set in your browser. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website or other websites. Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of personalized advertising from Google and other providers by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on our site. These partners include Google AdSense, Google AdExchange, Tribal Fusion and Sovrn. You may opt out of personalized advertising cookies from these partners by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

By accepting cookies and using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

## Data Security

Team Liquid runs on dedicated hosting servers which only a few trusted senior site staff have access to. Our servers are located in professionally managed and secure data centers in Canada and France.

## Children's Privacy

We do not allow children under the age of 13 to use our website. As there is user generated content, the site may be unsuitable for children.

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access your country, birthday and email through your Team Liquid profile page. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections on your behalf.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please talk to us by sending a Personal Message to any of the red named Moderators or contacting us via the "Contact" link at the bottom of the page.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
